export default [
  {
    question: "The first Easter eggs were dyed what color?",
    choice1: "Blue",
    choice2: "Green",
    choice3: "Purple",
    choice4: "Red",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the most popular Easter parade held each year?",
    choice1: "New York",
    choice2: "Utah",
    choice3: "Canada",
    choice4: "Texas",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the circumference of the worldâ€™s largest chocolate Easter egg?",
    choice1: "20 feet, 1.20 inches",
    choice2: "100 feet, 1.90 inches",
    choice3: "64 feet, 3.65 inches",
    choice4: "10 feet, 5 inches",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "In Switzerland, what animal delivers Easter eggs to kids?",
    choice1: "A rabbit",
    choice2: "A cuckoo",
    choice3: "A horse",
    choice4: "A bird",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Households each spend how much on average on Easter annually?",
    choice1: "$1,001",
    choice2: "201$",
    choice3: "820$",
    choice4: "131",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what country did the tradition of the Easter bunny originate?",
    choice1: "United States",
    choice2: "Germany",
    choice3: "Russia",
    choice4: "Dubai",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "When was the first White House Easter Egg Roll?",
    choice1: "1964",
    choice2: "1860",
    choice3: "1878",
    choice4: "1989",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the largest Easter egg museum in the world?",
    choice1: "Rome",
    choice2: "Paris",
    choice3: "London",
    choice4: "Poland",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "When Easter eggs were first dyed, it was to represent what?",
    choice1: "The colour of Jesus Christ's tombstone",
    choice2: "The blood of Jesus Christ",
    choice3: "The crucifix of Jesus Christ",
    choice4: "Mother Mary",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How many states consider Good Friday a holiday in the US?",
    choice1: "102",
    choice2: "57",
    choice3: "12",
    choice4: "5",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Buying what for Easter is said to bring good luck for the rest of the year?",
    choice1: "A new car",
    choice2: "Easter Eggs",
    choice3: "A new house",
    choice4: "New clothes",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Dyeing Easter eggs is a tradition that began in which country?",
    choice1: "Russia",
    choice2: "Ukraine",
    choice3: "Germany",
    choice4: "Algeria",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What dried fruit is in hot cross buns?",
    choice1: "Raisins",
    choice2: "Walnuts",
    choice3: "Almonds",
    choice4: "Cashews",
    answer: 1,
  },
];
